<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Quad</string>

    <string name="logout">Logout</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="email_validation">Enter Valid Email</string>
    <string name="first_name_validation">Name cannot be empty</string>
    <string name="last_name_validation">Invalid Lasy Name</string>
    <string name="phone_validation">Invalid Phone</string>
    <string name="college_validation">Invalid College Name</string>
    <string name="password_validation">Password does not meet creteria</string>
    <string name="password_duplication_validation">Passwords donot match</string>
    <string name="error_weak_password">Weak Password</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_email">Invalid email ID</string>
    <string name="error_user_exists">Email already registed</string>

    <string name="error_phone_length">Phone No. should be of length 10</string>

    <string name="user_creation_error">Unable to create user</string>
    <string name="authentication_error">Authentication Failed</string>
    <string name="fill_details_warning">Fill all details</string>
    <string name="password_mismatch_warning">Password donot match</string>
    <string name="permission_warning">Permission required to upload Pic</string>
    <string name="annon_user_auth_error">Annonymous User Authentication Failed</string>
    <string name="email_pass_incorrect_error">Either E-mail or password incorrect</string>
    <string name="invalid_username_error">Invalid Username</string>
    <string name="auth_failed_error">Authentication Failed</string>
    <string name="product_get_failed_error">Failed to get all products</string>
    
    <string name="register_password_validation">Password must contain atleast 6 characters</string>
    <string name="year_validation">Year should not be empty</string>
    <string name="error_empty_college">College name can not be empty</string>

    <string name="feedback_text">Hi\nI have downloaded Quad app and I would like to share my feedback for the app: /n1. </string>

    <string-array name="year_choices">
        <item>1st Year</item>
        <item>2nd Year</item>
        <item>3rd Year</item>
        <item>Final Year</item>
        <item>Super Final Year</item>
        <item>Alumni</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="temp">This is a real story of a young college girl who passed away last month in Coimbatore

Her name was Priya. She was hit by a truck.
She was working in a call center. She had a boy friend named Shankar.

Both of them were true lovers. They always talked on the phone.
You would never find her without handphone. In fact she also changed her cell connection from Aircell to Vodafone, so that both of them can be on the same network, and save on the cost.

 She used to spend half of the day talking with shankar. Priyas family knew about their relationship. . Shankar was very close to Priya s family as well. (Just imagine their love) .

Before she passed away she always told her friends  If I pass away please burn me with my handphone  she also said the same thing to her parents.

After her death, people cld nt carry her body, A lot of them tried to do so,but still can t. Everybody had tried to carry the body, the results were the same.
Eventually, they called a person known to one of their neighbours, who can speak with the soul of dead person and who was a friend of her father.

He took a stick and started speaking to himself slowly..
After a few minutes, he said  this girl misses something here.  Then her friends told that person about her intentions to burn her with her phone.

He then opened the grave box and place her phone and sim card inside the casket. After that they tried to carry the body. It was then moved easily and they then carried her into the van.

All of us were shocked. Priya s parents did not inform Shankar that Priya had passed away..

After 2 weeks Shankar called Priya s mom.....
Shankar :..... Aunty, I m coming home today.. Cook something nice for me.

Don t tell Priya that I m coming home today, I wanna surprise her.
Her mother replied.....  You come home first, I wanna tell you something very important.

After he came, they told him the truth about Priya.

Shankar thinks that they were playing a fool. He was laughing and said  don t try to fool me - tell Priya to come out, i have a gift for her. Please stop this nonsense .

Then they show him the original death certificate to him.

They gave him proof to make him believe. (Shankar started to sweat) He said...  Its not true.. We spoke yesterday.. She still calls me.

Shankar was shaking.
Suddenly, Shankar s phone rang..  see this is from Priya, see this....  he showed the phone to priya s family. all of them told him to answer. he talked using the loudspeaker mode..

All of them heard his conversation.
Loud and clear, no cross lines, no humming.
It is the actual voice of Priya there is no way others could use her sim card since it is nailed inside the grave box
They were so shocked and asked for the same person s
(who can speak with the soul of dead person) help again. He brought his master to solve this matter.

He his master worked for 5 hours.
Then they discovered one thing which really shocked them....

Vodafone has the best coverage
 Where ever you go, our network follows



Don t shout at me . . . I am also looking for the idiot who sent me this through whatsapp</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="products">Products</string>

</resources>
